[
  {
    "question": "Who was the first person to step on moon",
    "correct_answer": "Neil Armstrong",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Collins", "Buzz Aldrin ", "alan shepard"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At which year did Neil Armstrong stepped on moon",
    "correct_answer": "July 20, 1969",
    "incorrect_answers": ["July 20, 1969", "July 20, 1969", "July 20, 1969"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “exploit”?",
    "correct_answer": "verb",
    "incorrect_answers": ["interjection", "adjective", "noun"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “utility”?",
    "correct_answer": "noun",
    "incorrect_answers": ["adverb", "conjunction", "verb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “garrulous”?",
    "correct_answer": "adjective",
    "incorrect_answers": ["interjection", "preposition", "verb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “consolidate”?",
    "correct_answer": "verb",
    "incorrect_answers": ["adjective", "noun", "adverb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “diligently”?",
    "correct_answer": "adverb",
    "incorrect_answers": ["adjective", "noun", "verb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “frustratingly”?",
    "correct_answer": "adverb",
    "incorrect_answers": ["preposition", "noun", "verb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “beyond”?",
    "correct_answer": "preposition",
    "incorrect_answers": ["adverb", "adjectives", "verb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “beyond”?",
    "correct_answer": "preposition",
    "incorrect_answers": ["adverb", "adjectives", "verb"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the part of speech of the word “ricochet”?",
    "correct_answer": "noun",
    "incorrect_answers": ["adverb", "preposition", "verb"]
  }
]
